

# **NAURA AGUSTINA**

#### DIGITAL MARKETING ENTHUSIAST

Highly motivated bachelor of Chemical Engineering with almost 5 years of work experience. Passionate about Digital Marketing since crafting online business in 2020 and get used to created daily content marketing for it. Currently studying Digital Marketing and has driven the performance mindset and analytical skill. Was experienced as a leader and teaching the new established company system. This experiences has helped to improve skills on teamwork, strong analytical ability, leadership, time management, excellent communication skills, and ability to work effectively under pressure.

## Sukabumi, Indonesia

082258454585 | naura.agustina@outlook.com | linkedin.com/in/naura-agustina



# SKILLS SUMMARY

### **Brand Development**

- Built online business for snacks industry from scratch and conducted research to built brand voice and brand persona,
- Built dummy business for apparel industry and conducted competitive research, developed the social media's content pillar, and run the paid ads marketing.

#### Market Research

- Conducted qualitative and quantitative market research to define user persona,
- Conducted competitive research to discover market share.

## Social Media Management

- · Created and maintained daily posting schedule,
- Developed content pillar to become content briefs and implemented it as daily social media updates.

### Paid Ads

- Run 5 days paid campaign on FB Ads with limited budget for Traffic objective and result 401 link clicks, 10,869 impressions, and 3.69% CTR.
- Conducted keyword research to run 5 days paid campaign on Search Engine Marketing (SEM) and gained 548 impressions, 49 link clicks, and 8.94% CTR,
- Run Display Ads Campaign to spread brand awareness and gained 12,254 impressions.

#### SEC

 Complied all good SEO aspects such as meta descriptions, alt text, text length, internal links, etc.



## **EDUCATION**

Formal Education

### 08/2012 - 09/2016

Diploma IV of Chemical Engineering, Politeknik Negeri Bandung Non-formal Education

#### 03/2022 - Now

Digital Marketing Bootcamp Program, Dibimbing Digital Indonesia

- · Best Student of April 2022 and May 2022
- Scored 91 of 100 for FB Ads Technical Running (Best Presenter)
- Scored 92 of 100 for Google Ads Technical Running (Best Presenter)
- · Scored 92 of 100 for Content Planning Marketing



## **EXPERIENCE**

#### 03/2021 - 01/2022

#### Marketing Supervisor at PT Glostar Indonesia

- Offered and supplied goods to corporates such as PT Parkland World Indonesia, Pou Yuen Vietnam Co., Ltd., etc.,
- Worked closely with planning and production team to ensure overall stocks were available in timely manner,
- · Developed new company system in regards to SAP,
- Supplied goods on time with midsoles category, leading to manufacturing process reduction time and bigger productioncapacity in the same duration of time,
- Supervised and trained junior marketing staff for SAP operation.

#### 12/2016 - 05/2020

#### Purchasing Staff at PT Chang Shin Indonesia

- · Managed purchase requisitions and orders,
- Ensured that all goods and services purchased comply with company policies,
- Prepared purchase orders,
- Managed existing vendors and evaluated supplier performance for defect rate and lead time KPI,
- Collaborated with warehouse team to sustain enough stock on synthetic and textile materials,
- Determined delivery method by considering designated production schedule,
- Monitored returns, damage replacements, and warranty claims.
- · Approved bill of payments



# CERTIFICATION

# 05/2022

Fundamentals of Digital Marketing Google Digital Garage Certification

#### 04/2022

Intro to Digital Marketing
RevoU (PT Revolusi Citra Edukasi)